# Alirizo Karimov

## **Junior Software Engineer**

Uzbekistan, Bukhara, alirizok6@gmail.com +998 997072820 Audacious, motivated, and highly professional, Alirizo is a skilled junior full-stack React/Python software developer with 2+ years of experience. He is familiar with working in a team environment as well as individually. Alirizo strives to always be learning and enjoys using brand new technologies in his projects.

## Professional Experience

#### **Pandarium WEB**

Backend Junior Developer (2021 - 2022)

- Worked with websockets and crypto bots
- Did REST API's and documented, tested
   Optimized queries and found leaks

#### MondayLabs

Junior Software Developer (2020 - 2021)

- Helped the team and did code reviews
- Solved complex mobile application and web programming tasks and lead the way to the team

**U**unior Software Developer (2020 - 2021)

Participated in projects did light tasks on the backend and frontend

Supported the project and fixed minor bugs

Trainee (2019)

Assisted the development of multiple web and mobile applications.

Assisted the training of graduate interns in development processes.

### **Professional Qualifications**

## Tech Stack

Frontend web development (React)
Mobile development (React Native)
Backend development (Django, DRF)
DevOps (AWS, Git, Heroku)

#### References

Shakirov Saidravshan CEO, MondayLabs +998913106622